{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Electrical Outlet \u0026 Switch Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40226/":{"taskOID":40226,"originalTaskOID":40226,"setID":533,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6195,"questionDisplayText":"Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8073,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","answerDisplayText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8071,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","answerDisplayText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200361,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500240,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical fixtures ","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What electrical fixtures are included in this project? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"What electrical fixtures are included in this project? (Check all that apply)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8078,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Switches","answerDisplayText":"Switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200362,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior lights","answerDisplayText":"Interior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4486,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outlets","answerDisplayText":"Outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8082,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior lights","answerDisplayText":"Exterior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8096,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Other fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8090,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6195,"questionDisplayText":"Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8073,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","answerDisplayText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8071,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","answerDisplayText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200361,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8073,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","answerDisplayText":"Repair or replace an old switch, fixture or outlet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Install new switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8071,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","answerDisplayText":"Troubleshoot an electrical problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200361,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","answerDisplayText":"Move switches, fixtures or outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500240,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical fixtures ","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What electrical fixtures are included in this project? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"What electrical fixtures are included in this project? (Check all that apply)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8078,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Switches","answerDisplayText":"Switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200362,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior lights","answerDisplayText":"Interior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4486,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outlets","answerDisplayText":"Outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8082,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior lights","answerDisplayText":"Exterior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8096,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Other fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8090,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8078,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling fan or chandelier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Switches","answerDisplayText":"Switches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200362,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior lights","answerDisplayText":"Interior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4486,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outlets","answerDisplayText":"Outlets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8082,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior lights","answerDisplayText":"Exterior lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8096,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Other fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8090,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Bath or attic exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40226/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40226,"taskName":"Electrical Switches, Outlets \u0026 Fixtures - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install Electrical Switches, Outlets, and Fixtures","xmTaskDescriptor":"Electrical Outlet \u0026 Switch Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":316,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Electrical Fixtures Outlets Switches Electrician","textMessagingName":"Install Elec Fixture","rolloverLongDesc":"This includes running all standard wiring \u0026 components in existing rooms that have already been finished with drywall, paneling, plaster or similar finishes. Involves fishing wires through existing walls. Note separate categories for repair work, landscape lighting \u0026 running new wires in unfinished spaces.","rolloverShortDesc":"Switches, lights, outlets, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Electrical Switches, Outlets, and Fixtures.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Electrical Outlet Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install or Repair Electrical Outlets, Switches, Fixtures","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Electric Outlets \u0026 Fixtures Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Electrical Switches, Outlets \u0026 Fixtures - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Electrician Need","urlName":"Install-or-Repair-Electrical-Switches-and-Outlets","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Electrical Outlet \u0026 Light Switch Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Outlets, Switches, Fixtures","searchKeywords":"Electric, Electrician, lighting, light, chandelier, recessed, sconces, Fluorescent, track, doorbell","emcCategoryOid":-12026,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":533,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}